Sumit Yadav

Kathmandu, Bāgmatī, Nepal



rockerritesh4@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/rockerritesh



9819856148



https://sumityadav.com.np

Summary

Diligent Computer Engineering student familiar with helping created detailed application codes. Extensive colaboration with developers to draft and test programs for in-field rollout, Deep knowledge of Python, Machine learning and Computer Vision. Offers specialized ability for generating automation frameworks and procedures.

Experience



GAN Mentor

DeepLearning.Al Aug 2021 - Present (7 months +)



Data Science Researcher

PDSC

2021 - Present (1 year 2 months +)



Al and Robotics Member

Robotics Association of Nepal 2020 - Present (2 years 2 months +)



Joint Secretary

NTBNS Pulchowk Campus 2020 - Dec 2021 (2 years)

Education



IOE PULCHOWK CAMPUS

Bachelor in computer engineering, Computer Engineering 2019 - 2024



Kathmandu Bernhardt College

+2, Mathematics and Computer Science 2017 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Deep Learning with Tensorflow - IBM

f3b73c6322e9491db5dee922963a5052

- Support Vector Machines with scikit-learn Coursera 8037170bca5756040ca5b7299218d596
- Unsupervised Machine Learning for Customer Market Segmentation Coursera https://coursera.org/share/77d06fddf01b3dfb808d7cfd073ead5d
- Neural Networks and Deep Learning Coursera
- Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization Coursera

 0c0388a3be859c5f7e26293e38b362e8
- Structuring Machine Learning Projects Coursera d636dde4a8d2302143ee447410de1247
- Convolutional Neural Networks Coursera 63855bdb13f4f767c1034106a973da07
- Sequence Models Coursera 6eef8892a952ce5fc2ddcc8e97d8dede
- Generate Synthetic Images with DCGANs in Keras Coursera
- Image Understanding with TensorFlow on GCP Coursera
- **Deep Learning Specialization** Coursera 0f949089d595e1c948ae0d8ddac84a8c
- Build Basic Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Coursera a4ece62c1ee5d6a81a2feac8ea7895c9
- Build Better Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Coursera eaea800c2ccce4fac22f8525efa95463
- Apply Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Coursera
- Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Coursera

Introduction to Machine Learning - Coursera

11f453b76a5a495dc340bc4f700654f8

Object Localization with TensorFlow - Coursera

7330618afe8bf9080b793c459b9e57df

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Machine Learning • Deep Learning • Data Science • Data Analysis • Computer Vision • C (Programming Language)

Honors & Awards

Capture The Flag - LOCUS

Feb 2022

We topped in advance level CTF.

DATARUSH- LOCUS 2021 - LOCUS

Jan 2022

We scored second position in Datarush.